export interface IQuestion {
  id: number;
  question: string;
  answer: string[];
  correctAnswer: string;
}

export const Quiz1: IQuestion[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the prophet that restored Paul's sight?",
    answer: ["Nathan", "Ananiah", "samuel", "Micah"],
    correctAnswer: "Ananiah",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Who was the first man to get drunk in the bible?",
    answer: ["Adam", "Methuselah", "Jeroboam", "Noah"],
    correctAnswer: "Noah",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "'I can do all things, through Christ whom strengthens me...', can be gotten from?",
    answer: ["Matt. 23:10", "Eph. 3:20", "Phil. 4:13", "James 4:1"],
    correctAnswer: "Phil. 4:13",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Jacob I like, but ________ I hate",
    answer: ["Esau", "Napthali", "Edom", "Reuben"],
    correctAnswer: "Esau",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "'Remember the Sabbath Day to keep it holy...', Where can this be found in the bible?",
    answer: ["Exodus 20:8", "John 3:16", "lam. 14:20", "Prov. 22:6"],
    correctAnswer: "Exodus 20:8",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "How many days and nights did Moses stay with God in Mount Sinai?",
    answer: [
      "3days and 3nights",
      "20 days and 10 nights",
      "40 days and 40 nights",
      "Just a day and a night",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "40 days and 40 nights",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Who was the first man that prayed and fire came down from heaven?",
    answer: ["Elijah", "David", "Elisha", "Jeremiah"],
    correctAnswer: "David",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Who was the first king of Israel?",
    answer: ["Josiah", "Ahab", "David", "Saul"],
    correctAnswer: "Saul",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Who held Angel Gabriel hostage when he was sent to deliver God's report to Daniel?",
    answer: [
      "Prince of Edom",
      "Prince of Persia",
      "Prince of darkness",
      "Asmodeus",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Prince of Persia",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "who rode the talking donkey?",
    answer: ["Barak", "Balak", "Balaam", "Borah"],
    correctAnswer: "Balak",
  },
];
export const Quiz2: IQuestion[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the full meaning of URL?",
    answer: [
      "Uniform Retoriated Lines",
      "Unanimous Retrieval Laplace",
      "Uniform Resource Locator",
      "Unanimous Require Leakage",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Uniform Resource Locator",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Who is known as the father of modern computer?",
    answer: [
      "Charles Parker",
      "Steve Newbriggs",
      "Von Neuumann",
      "Charles Babbage",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Charles Babbage",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which is the most correct representation of classification of Computer according to size?",
    answer: [
      "mini>micro>mainFrame>Super",
      "micro>mini>super>mainframe",
      "mainframe>super>mini>micro",
      "super>mainfram>mini>micro",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "super>mainfram>mini>micro",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "________ are special lines in a computer for transferring signals/data from one part of the computer to another?",
    answer: ["wires", "BUS", "cables", "NOTA"],
    correctAnswer: "BUS",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is termed 'THE BRAIN' of the computer system?",
    answer: ["System Unit", "Motherboard", "CPU", "ICs"],
    correctAnswer: "CPU",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is termed 'THE HEART' of the computer system?",
    answer: ["System Unit", "Motherboard", "CPU", "ICs"],
    correctAnswer: "Motherboard",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "The Integrated Circuit (IC) composes of ___________",
    answer: ["Electrons", "Semi-conductors", "Semi-electrons", "quarks"],
    correctAnswer: "Semi-conductors",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the Full meaning of R.A.M?",
    answer: [
      "Random Access Memory",
      "Random Authenticated Memory",
      "Random Associated Mint",
      "Read Access Memory",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Random Access Memory",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the Full meaning of H.D.D?",
    answer: [
      "Hard Drive Disk",
      "Hard Disk Drive",
      "Hard Disk Ditch",
      "Hard Drain Drag",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hard Disk Drive",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Example of input devices includes all except __________",
    answer: ["Mouse", "Joystick", "Scanner", "Plotter"],
    correctAnswer: "Plotter",
  },
];
export const Quiz3: IQuestion[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What year did Nigeria gain her independence",
    answer: ["1980", "1990", "1960", "2000"],
    correctAnswer: "1960",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Who was the first man to work on the moon?",
    answer: ["Robert Shelby", "Neil Armstrong", "Aristotle", "James Foxx"],
    correctAnswer: "Neil Armstrong",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who explored the New world?",
    answer: [
      "Iris Coleman",
      "George Brian",
      "Christopher Columbus",
      "Charles Flitcher",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Christopher Columbus",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Who is considered the inventor of electric light?",
    answer: ["Thomas Edison", "Micheal Faraday", "Louis Freeman", "John calle"],
    correctAnswer: "Thomas Edison",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "When did the First world war started?",
    answer: ["1908", "1932", "1914", "1970"],
    correctAnswer: "1914",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "In which Ocean did the Titanic Sink?",
    answer: [
      "Pacific Ocean",
      "Atlantic Ocean",
      "Condor Ocean",
      "deep sea ocean",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Atlantic Ocean",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "The opium war  was a battle between which two countries? ",
    answer: [
      "England and China",
      "Germany and Russia",
      "Thailand and Japan",
      "Argentina and Mexico",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "England and China",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which Country did Covid-19 pandemic started from?",
    answer: ["Congo", "America", "China", "Japan"],
    correctAnswer: "China",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Where did the statue of Liberty come from?",
    answer: ["Mexico", "China", "America", "France"],
    correctAnswer: "France",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What year was Nelson Mandela freed from prison?",
    answer: ["1999", "1995", "1990", "1998"],
    correctAnswer: "1999",
  },
];
